Guide to the Kathleen George Papers, 1962-2014 CTC.2012.02
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Writing Career, 1961-2014; III.
  - Unpublished Works, 1961-2001; 3.
    - Undergraduate and Graduate writing and other materials, 1961-1964
      The play A Glass of Wine was produced at the student union during.
      - A Glass of Wine (Box 75, Folder 3)
      - ***********Gypsy - Director's submitted report, July 30, 1963 (Box 75, Folder 4)
      - Manfred (Box 75, Folder 5)
      - Other student work (Box 75, Folder 6)
      - The Tree House (Box 75, Folder 7)
      - Undergraduate writing - Brackenridge Hall (Box 75, Folder 8)
      - Undergraduate writing - Holland Hall, 1964 (Box 75, Folder 9)
      - Undergraduate writing - Pitt Johnstown, 1961 (Box 75, Folder 10)
      - Untitled play (Box 75, Folder 11)
      - Untitled play (Box 75, Folder 12)
    - Where Storytellers Meet, 1995
      This unpublished work is a collection of personal essays on narrative and drama.
      - Correspondence, January 11, 1995 (Box 75, Folder 13)
      - Drafts (Box 75, Folder 14)
      - Grant proposal (Box 75, Folder 15)
      - Reader's report, February 1995 (Box 75, Folder 16)
  - Writing Related, 1980-2012; 4.
    Within this subseries are materials related to Kathleen George's writing career. These files are not related to a specific work, but do illustrate the immense amount of work that is also required after a work has been written. Included are grant applications, fellowship and award submissions, materials on various writing colonies, conferences, short fiction journal submissions, etc.
    - Association of Writers & Writing Programs, February 2011 (Box 75, Folder 17)
    - Bouchercon mystery convention, 2005-2012 (Box 75, Folder 18)
    - Copyright Office forms - blank (Box 76, Folder 1)
    - Dance at St. Theresa's - Oral interpretation at Calvin College, October 1993 (Box 76, Folder 2)
    - Fellowships, grants, prizes, awards, etc., 1980-1983 (Box 76, Folder 3)
    - Fellowships, grants, prizes, awards, etc., 1989-2000 (Box 76, Folder 4-5)
    - Fiction workshop, 1986 (Box 76, Folder 6)
    - Kellogg National Fellowship, 1980 (Box 76, Folder 7)
    - Ligonier Valley Writers Conference, 1996, 2006 (Box 76, Folder 8)
    - List of time periods in various short stories (Box 76, Folder 9)
    - Literary agents and editors, 1980-1999 (Box 76, Folder 10-11)
    - Penwriters conference programs, 2009-11 (Box 76, Folder 12)
    - Pirate's Alley Faulkner Society, Inc. - Conferences, 2009 (Box 77, Folder 1)
    - Pirate's Alley Faulkner Society, Inc. - Novel prize, 1992-1994, 1998 (Box 77, Folder 2)
    - Places to submit fiction, 2001-2004 (Box 77, Folder 3)
    - Playwriting workshop - University of Northern Colorado, 1993 (Box 77, Folder 4)
    - Poets & Writers Inc., 1980 (Box 77, Folder 5)
    - Ragdale Foundation - Evaluations, February 2006 (Box 77, Folder 6)
    - Short story fiction - Submissions for publication and responses, 1980-1989 (Box 77, Folder 7-15)
    - Short story fiction - Submissions for publication and responses, 1990-1995 (Box 78, Folder 1-12)
    - Short story fiction - Submissions for publication and responses, 1996-1999 (Box 79, Folder 1-5)
    - Submissions checklist (Box 79, Folder 6)
    - Temple University - Reading, 2001 (Box 79, Folder 7)
    - Thrillerfest 2012 panelist, July 2012 (Box 79, Folder 8)
    - University of Pittsburgh at Johnstown - Reading, 1997 (Box 79, Folder 9)
    - Website content, 2007-2011 (Box 79, Folder 10-11)
    - Website content - Restaurant tour, 2011 (Box 79, Folder 12)
    - Writer's colonies and residencies, 1980-2000 (Box 79, Folder 13-14)
- Oversized Materials, 1975-2012; IV.
  - Her First American poster, April 2005 (Box 80, Folder 1)
  - The Johnstown Girls - Bird's-Eye View of Conemaugh Valley From Nineveh to the Lake - Facsimile of Alex Y. Lee map (Box 80, Folder 2)
  - The Johnstown Girls Research - Newspaper clippings, 1979-1997 (Box 80, Folder 3)
  - Mystery Writers of America award - Certificate of nomination, April 29, 2010 (Box 80, Folder 4)
  - Newspaper articles about George, 1975-2012 (Box 80, Folder 5)
  - Newspaper articles by George, 2007 (Box 80, Folder 6)
  - Pittsburgh Noir posters (Box 80, Folder 7)
  - Published works - Reviews and other clippings, 1980-2004 (Box 80, Folder 8)
  - Published works - Reviews and other clippings, 2010-2012 (Box 80, Folder 9)
  - Readings and appearances - Posters, 1999-2011 (Box 80, Folder 10)